♪ We
♪ Are the Crystal Gems
♪ We'll always save the day
Steven:♪ And if you think we can't
♪ We'll always find a way
♪ That's why the people
♪ Of this world
♪ Believe in
♪ Garnet
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl
天气不错啊,是吧?
Lovely day, isn't it?
还行吧
Yeah, I guess.
你造,我爸爸告诉过我
Ya know,uh, my dad told me
到了一定岁数这种事就会发生的
I should probably expect this at some point,
但我也没想到会是一夜之间那么快
but I didn't think it would happen overnight.
对啊,不错
Right, yeah.
康妮!我秃了!
Connie, I'm bald!
哦 发生了什么事?
Oh. What happened?
没事 只是个笑话而已
Nothing.It was just a joke.
哦,好吧
Oh, okay.
嘿,你还好吗?
Hey, are you okay?
史蒂文,康妮!
Steven, Connie!
希望你们准备好学习今天的特殊课程了
I hope you two are ready for today's special lesson.
哦,不,我是不是应该带什么东西来着?
Oh, no, was I supposed to bring something?
带上自己就好
Just yourselves.
石榴会参与旁听
Garnet is going to sit in.
能看你俩作为史蒂翁妮战斗她非常激动
She's very excited to see you fight as Stevonnie.
哦!对啊!
Oh! Right!
融合训练
Fusion training.
我做了个口号板
I made a sign.
这面是为你们俩加油
This side is for both of you.
这面是为史蒂翁妮加油
And this sideis for Stevonnie.
一体两面的
It's two signs in one.
融合口号
A fusion sign.
融合笑话!
Fusion joke!
♪♪
准备好了吗?
Ready, kids?
好了,老师
Yes, ma'am!
-康妮!-好了,老师!
-Connie!-Yes, ma'am!
史蒂文!康妮!喔!
Ste-ven! Con-nie!Whoo!
启动融合舞蹈
Initiating fusion dance.
♪♪
来打我啊,孩子们
Come at me, children.
♪♪
不如跳舞
Let's dance.
准备...开始!
Let us...begin!
哈?
Huh?
哦!
Oh!
好棒!
All right!
史蒂翁妮有悬浮能力了!
Stevonnie's got floating powers!
是时候干掉你了!
Time to finish the job!
哈?我很抱歉!
Huh?I'm sorry!
史蒂文!康妮!
Steven! Connie!
发-发生啥事?
W-What happened?
嗯啊!
Mmmuh!
康妮,等下!
Connie, wait!
嘿,你怎么了?
Hey, what's wrong?
我在学校做了很糟糕的事
I did something terrible at school,
现在不知道该怎么办
and I don't know what to do.
嘛,听起来不像你的风格
Well, that doesn't sound like you.
发生了什么?
What happened?
我打了一个同学
I beat someone up.
啥?
What?
一个不认识的小孩
A kid I didn't know.
他在走廊上撞到了我
He just bumped into me in the hallway.
我吓了一跳,然后战斗本能被激发了
I was so startled,my training instincts kicked in.
我反击了
I just reacted.
我觉得太丢人了,就跑掉了
I was so embarrassed,I just ran away.
但是你不是有意伤害他的!
But you didn't mean to hurt him!
我知道那种感觉
I know what it's like.
有时候,你会不小心伤害到别人
Sometimes,you hurt people by accident.
你-你不去想它就好了
Y-you just have to try not to think about it.
先别说话
Hold the phone.
交给我来说
Now give the phone to me.
融合能正常存在,取决于平衡
For a fusion to work,there needs to be balance.
不平衡会导致你的融合
An imbalancecan cause your fusion
失去对现实的把握
to lose touch with reality,
产生各种幻觉,最终破碎解体
see things that aren't there,and eventually fall apart.
也就是说,你俩其中一个迷失的话,
That is to say,if one of you is falling apart,
你们的融合也会解体
your fusion will as well.
为了找到平衡,你们必须了解自己的情感
To find balance, you must understand your feelings.
为了了解自己的情感,你们需要透彻地看待它们
To understand your feelings,you must see them clearly
而不是逃避它们
without running from them.
透彻地看?
See them clearly?
我会展示的,不过首先,我们需要史蒂翁妮来
I'll show you,but first, we'll need Stevonnie.
-嗯-嗯
-Mm.-Mm.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
好的
Okay.
深呼吸
Breathe.
在这儿,在黑暗中,一切安好
Here, in darkness,everything's okay.
停紧涛声,任其自然褪去
Listen to the waves,and let them fade away.
一片思绪其来
Here comes a thought.
哈?Huh?
♪♪
♪花些时间去想下♪
♪ Take a momentto think of just ♪
♪爱和信任与接纳♪
♪ Flexibility,love, and trust ♪
♪花些时间去想下♪
♪ Take a momentto think of just ♪
♪爱和信任与接纳♪
♪ Flexibility,love, and trust ♪
♪细细思考♪
♪ Here comes a thought
♪你察觉与否
♪That might alarm you
♪他人话语
♪ What someone said
♪很使你难受
♪ And how it harmed you
♪琐事既已
♪ Something you did
♪结局却不明
♪ That failed to be charming ♪
♪说过的话，又突然轰鸣，你，哦
♪ Things that you said are suddenly swarming, and oh! ♪
♪不见光彩
♪ You're losing sight
♪失去对白
♪ You're losing touch
♪所有的琐事都显得那么不该
♪ All these little things seem to matter so much ♪
♪困惑中漂游
♪ That they confuse you
♪不想你迷走
♪ That I might lose you
♪花些时间去思考
♪ Take a moment,remind yourself ♪
♪来花些时间去寻找
♪ To take a moment and find yourself ♪
♪花些时间去探讨
♪ Take a moment to ask yourself ♪
♪我是否因此破碎掉
♪ If this is how we fall apart ♪
♪你不要，你不要
♪ But it's not,but it's not ♪
♪你不要，你不要，你不要
♪ But it's not, but it's not,but it's not ♪
♪别逃跑，别逃跑
♪ It's okay, it's okay
♪别逃跑，别逃跑，别逃跑
♪ It's okay, it's okay,it's okay ♪
♪你不应，你不应
♪ You've got nothing,got nothing, ♪
♪你不应，你不应恐惧
♪ Got nothing,got nothing to fear ♪
♪我在这儿，我在这儿，我在这儿
♪ I'm here,I'm here, I'm here ♪
♪细细思考，很令我惊异
♪ Here comes a thought that might alarm me ♪
♪他人话语
♪ What someone said
♪伤透我心底
♪ And how it harmed me
♪琐事既已
♪ Something I did
♪结局却不行
♪ That failed to be charming ♪
♪说过的话
♪ Things that I said
♪突然又轰鸣
♪ Are suddenly swarming
♪我，哦，我不见光彩
♪ And, oh,I'm losing sight ♪
♪我失去对白
♪ I'm losing touch
♪所有的琐事都显得那么不该
♪ All these little thingsseem to matter so much ♪
♪困惑中逃避
♪ That they confuse me
♪怕失去自己
♪ That I might lose me
♪花些时间去思考
♪ Take a moment,remind yourself ♪
♪来花些时间去寻找
♪ To take a moment and find yourself ♪
♪花些时间来探讨
♪ Take a momentand ask yourself ♪
♪我们是否因此破碎掉
♪ If this is how we fall apart ♪
♪你不要，你不要
♪ But it's not, but it's not
♪你不要，你不要，你不要
♪ But it's not, but it's not,but it's not ♪
♪别逃跑，别逃跑
♪ It's okay, it's okay
♪别逃跑，别逃跑，别逃跑
♪ It's okay, it's okay,it's okay ♪
♪我不应，我不应
♪ I've got nothing,got nothing ♪
♪我不应，我不应恐惧
♪ Got nothing,got nothing to fear ♪
♪我在这儿，我在这儿，我在这儿
♪ I'm here, I'm here, I'm here
♪这思绪没多少
♪ And it was just a thought
♪没多少，没多少
♪ Just a thought,just a thought ♪
♪别逃跑，别逃跑
♪ It's okay, it's okay,
♪别逃跑，别逃跑，别逃跑
♪ It's okay, it's okay,it's okay ♪
♪可以瞧，可以瞧，可以瞧
♪ We can watch, we can watch,we can watch, ♪
♪可以瞧它飞过
♪ We can watch them go by
♪在这儿，在这儿，在这儿
♪ From here,from here, from here ♪
♪花些时间去想下
♪Take a moment to think of just ♪
♪爱和信任与接纳
♪ Flexibility,love, and trust ♪
♪花些时间去想下
♪ Take a moment to think of just ♪
♪爱和信任与接纳
♪ Flexibility,love,and trust ♪
♪♪
史蒂文,我准备好训练了!
Steven,I'm ready to train!
我很高兴和石榴谈话了
I'm so glad we talked to Garnet.
我想到该怎么做了!
I really figured outwhat I needed to do!
我和杰夫谈过了!
I talked to Jeff!
他叫杰夫,顺便说一下
That's his name,by the way.
哇,你做到了
Whoa, you did it.
我道歉了,他也理解我了
I apologizedand he understood!
他事实上还想让我给他表演几招
He actually wanted to know if I could show him some moves.
-很不错啊
-That's great!
想来真有趣
It's funny.
我花了那么多时间沉浸在不安中
I spent all that time feeling bad
却没有采取任何行动
instead of doing something.
好像我越是试着不去想它
It's like I was trying not to think about it,
事情就变得越糟
and that just made it worse.
现在我思绪清晰了,
Now that I've got a clear head,
我们作为史蒂翁妮会表现出色的
we'll do so much better as Stevonnie.
不说了,我得换衣服了!
Anyway,I'm gonna change!
♪♪
很棒的技巧,史蒂翁妮
Great technique, Stevonnie.
继续保持!
Keep it up!
谢谢夸奖,老师!
Thanks, ma'am!
嗨呀!
Hyah!
呃,啊...
Uh, uh...
哦,哦,啊...
Oh, oh, uh...
哦,不
Oh, no.
又开始了!
It's happening again!
她是谁啊?
Who was that?
是铋斯姆--史蒂文--哦,不
Bismuth -- Steven -- oh, no.
这次是我的问题了!
It's coming from me now!
-史蒂翁妮!-啊
-Stevonnie!-U-uh!
深呼吸!
Breathe!
发生了什么?
What's going on?
他们怎么了?
What's happening to them?
他们能做到的!
They've got this!
对,我-我能-呃
Y-yeah,I'm...I'm...ugh.
铁石英
Jasper.
我-我试着帮你来的
I-I tried to help you.
是你选择不听的
You wouldn't listen.
我-我说过让你停下!
I--I told you to stop!
我-我也别无选择!
I-I had no choice!
我-我很抱歉!我不该--
I-I'm sorry.I shouldn't be --
不!没关系的!
No! It's okay!
想这些事没关系的!
It's okay to think about it!
我以为没关系的,但是我承受不住!
I thought I could,but it's so much!
我做不到!
I can't do it!
啊!
Ahh!
Ah!
不
No.
史蒂翁妮!
Stevonnie!
我们在坠落!
We're falling!
史蒂文,和我融合!
Steven, let's fuse!
我们能悬浮的 我们会没事的!
We can hover.We'll be okay!
史蒂文?
Steven?
我没有想伤害任何人!
I didn't want to hurt anyone!
我很抱歉!
I'm sorry!
她们没有一个接受我的帮助!
None of them would let me help them!
我也别无选择!
I had no choice!
没关系的!
It's okay!
不!有关系!
No, it's not!
但你回想这些事是可以的!
But it's okay to think about it!
感觉太难受了
It feels so bad.
那也没关系!That's okay, too!
当时你也没有其他的选择!
There was nothing else you could have done!
我不想感觉这么糟
I don't want to feel this way.
你不得不
You have to.
你需要正面对待这些糟糕的情感
You have to be honest about how bad it feels
这样才能跨过去
so you can move on.
我就是这么做的
That's how it was for me.
好吧
Okay.
深呼吸就好
Just breathe.
♪♪
嗯-
Mm-mm-mm.
我在这里
I'm here.
♪♪